<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Minute on the Mic</title>
    <link>https://aminuteonthemic.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Minute on the Mic</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2020, A Minute on the Mic; all rights reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 17:08:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aminuteonthemic.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 2: Working from Home</title>
      <link>https://aminuteonthemic.com/episodes/episode2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aminuteonthemic.com/episodes/episode2/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the second episode of A Minute on the Mic! Our question this round is &amp;ldquo;How do you work from home safely, successfully, and happily?&amp;rdquo;
Our guests are Aaron Aldrich, Jeremy Meiss, Daniel Maher, Chuck Tomasi, Andrew Barnes, Chris Short, Quintessence Anx, and Dawn Parzych &amp;ndash; with a very special guest!
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://aminuteonthemic.com/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aminuteonthemic.com/process/</guid>
      <description>Thanks for joining me on this adventure! This doc will be updated with the most current guidelines and details on how to participate.
Question Crowdsourcing Process The call for questions will go out within an hour after each episode posts on the hashtag #AMinuteOnTheMic on Twitter. For now, these posts are going out on my personal account.
Video Guidelines  Videos MUST be 60 seconds or less (59.99 seconds, the three nines of mic time).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Episode 1: Toil</title>
      <link>https://aminuteonthemic.com/episodes/episode1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aminuteonthemic.com/episodes/episode1/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s the first episode of A Minute on the Mic! Our question this round is &amp;ldquo;If you could eliminate one source of toil, what would it be?&amp;rdquo;
Our guests are JJ Asghar, Chris Short, Kat Cosgrove, Ken Mugrage, Matty Stratton, Dawn Parzych, Paul Czarkowski, Quintessence Anx, Leon Stigter, and Sasha Rosenbaum.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About A Minute on the Mic</title>
      <link>https://aminuteonthemic.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aminuteonthemic.com/about/</guid>
      <description>A Minute on the Mic is a curated video series where the curator (Laura Santamaria) takes a crowd-sourced question from Twitter, finds experts, and gives each expert a chance to answer the question in one minute in a recorded response. Then, all of those responses are compiled into a single video and released for everyone to watch.
In curating these videos, I hope that we can start getting a sense of how we collectively work, how we collectively think, and how we collectively can go do great things.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>